Doug? Oh, yeah. I don't know. I mean,
you know, he's nice and funny, but...
- Can I get you started with some drinks?
- No. Bzzz.
- You were saying, "But..."?
- I'd like a drink.
Just say the "but" thing about Doug,
and then I'll get her back.
Okay, well, it...
I don't know. It's just me.
(Penny:)I'm still getting over this break-up
with Kurt.
(Penny:)And this thing with Doug
would just be rebound sex.
(Leonard:)Ugh. Don't get me started
on rebound sex.
(Penny:)It's just... It's my pattern.
(Penny:)I break up, then I find some cute guy...
(Penny:)...and then it's just
36 meaningless hours of...
(Penny:)Well, you know.
(Leonard:)I'm not sure that I do. Um...
Is that one 36-hour experience
or is that 36 hours spread out over...
...say, one glorious summer?
(Penny:)No. It's usually over a weekend.
(Penny:)And trust me,
you do not feel good after it.
(Leonard:)Well, chafing, right?